<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Furkan Ercevik</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Furkan Ercevik</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 12:57:06 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>STLKER</title>
      <link>/projects/stlker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 12:57:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/stlker/</guid>
      <description>STLKER STLKER is a stock tracking application that utilizes RESTful and gRPC microservices to serve content neatly in the command line via curl and grpcurl
About This project is mostly made in Golang using the Gorilla Mux and GORM frameworks. It also implements several other features that are common in many webservices today. Moreover, this project was completed in order to develop a more complete understanding of microservice architecture, as well as to create something that can be used directly from the command line without much parsing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Furkan Ercevik, and I am a Computer Science B.S. student at UCSC. I am currently taking CSE 115A (Introduction to Software Engineering), CSE 140 (Artificial Intelligence), and CSE 180 (Database Systems I).
I am experienced in Golang, Rust, Python, C/C++, Haskell, JAVA, Docker, CI/CD, gRPC, REST, AWS Ecosystem, Agile Methodologies, and more. I am currently using the tokio and pnet crates in my Rust project nazar. In the past, I&amp;rsquo;ve utilized the Gorilla Mux and GORM frameworks in Golang and Flask, FastAPI, &amp;amp; Pycord in Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>nazar - an intrusion detection system Tools Rust, tokio, pnet, Computer Networking, Packet Parsing, Computer Security, SQL
Links GitHub link STLKER - a stock tracking application Tools gRPC, REST, Gorilla Mux, GORM, Golang, PostgreSQL, Redis, OpenApi/Swagger, Docker, AWS, GitHub
Links GitHub link
Article
Wave - a CLI application to load test REST-ful APIs Tools Golang, Cobra, Concurrency, YAML file parsing, Docker, En/Decryption, GitHub
Links GitHub link VPath - pathfinding visualizing program Tools Python, Pygame, GitHub</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
